Guide to the Inge Morath Photographs and Papers GEN MSS 996
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1896-2001; 1; 707430; 136.99 Linear Feet (550 boxes)
  - Color Transparencies, 707553
    - General Slides, 707554
      - Western and Eastern Europe, 707846
        - Romania, 707880
          - Bucharest, Ploiești, Horezu monastery, Răşinari, villages, 1958; 707883; 3 Folders (Box 437)
            1958-09, 1958-15
          - Chuhea, Voronet, Certeze, 1958; 707882; 4 Folders (Box 438)
            1958-15
          - Sucevița church, Romanian churches, Danube Delta, 1958; 707881; 3 Folders (Box 439)
        - Germany, 707874
          - Danube in Germany, 1954-1959; 707879; 2 Folders (Box 439)
            1954-13, 1959-26
          - Berlin Wall, Dresden, Jüdischer Friedhof Weißensee, 1989-1996; 707878 (Box 440)
            1989-18, 1993-10, 1996-03
          - Dresden, 1997; 707877 (Box 440)
          - Berlin, undated; 707876; 3 Folders (Box 440)
          - Altzella, Hatmaker clocks, Munich, Hainburg, Grein, Darmstadt, undated; 707875; 6 Folders (Box 441)
        - Austria, 707863
          - Austria, Carnival in Snow, Danube, Vienna, New Viennese Baroque, 1955-1959; 707873; 3 Folders (Box 441)
            1955-05, 1958-17, 1959-12
          - Prague/Slovakia, 1993; 707872 (Box 441)
            1993-10, 1993-11
          - Danube in Austria, 1959; 707871 (Box 442)
            1959-27
          - Refugee camps, 1960; 707870 (Box 442)
          - Danube in Vienna, 1961; 707869; 2 Folders (Box 442)
            1961-18
          - Danube, Vienna, 1967; 707868 (Box 442)
          - Vienna, 1975-1992; 707867; 5 Folders (Box 443)
            1975-09, 1978-02, 1980-09, 1992-07
          - Salzburg, 1975-1997; 707866 (Box 443)
            1978-02
          - Vienna, 1978-1980; 707865 (Box 443)
          - Miscellaneous, 1959-1993; 707864; 2 Folders (Box 444)
        - Czechoslovakia, 1958, undated; 707862; 2 Folders (Box 444)
          1958-18
        - Yugoslavia, 1958; 707861; 2 Folders (Box 444)
          1958-16
        - Danube Region, 707857
          - Story list, undated; 707860 (Box 445)
          - Lake Constance, Danube in Vienna, 1959-1994; 707859 (Box 445)
            1959-25, 1961-18, 1993-09, 1994-04
          - Romania, Bulgaria, Danube, 1994-1995; 707858; 4 Folders (Box 446)
            1994-04, 1994-12, 1995-12
        - Soviet Union/Russia, 707849
          - Lithuania, Vilnius, Kaunas, 1985-1986; 707856; 2 Folders (Box 447)
          - Pasternak book, 1977-1979; 707855 (Box 447)
          - Arthur Miller, Moscow, Leningrad, Samarkand, First Issyk-Voz, 1965-1986; 707854; 4 Folders (Box 448)
            1965-05, 1967-11, 1985-14
          - "Visit to Vladimir and Susdal and Armenia," "Inge Morath Show in Moscow, building of Union of Photojournalists," "Trip to Moscow, Kalinin (Tver) and Vilnius and Launus in Lithuania," "Peter Brook's production of The Cherry Orchard by Anton Chekhov at the Taganka Theater in Moscow", 1987-1989; 707853; 4 Folders (Box 449)
            1987-07, 1988-07, 1989-11, 1989-12,
          - "Trip to the Soviet Union", 1989; 707852; 4 Folders (Box 450)
          - "Visit to Vladimir and Susdal and Armenia," "Trip to the Soviet Union (with Progress Publishers)," "Some portraits of Arthur Miller with a new hat," "Trips to Moscow and Peredelkind on the Occasion of Boris Pasternak's 100th Birthday", 1965-1990; 707851; 4 Folders (Box 451)
            1987-07, 1989-10, 1989-17, 1990-04
          - Russia, "Belogradcik," miscellaneous, 1965-1990; 707850; 3 Folders (Box 452)
            1965-05, 1967-11, 1989-11, 1989-17
        - Sweden, 707847
          - Uppsala, 1960; 707848 (Box 452)
            1960-08
      - United States, 707817
        - Alaska, 1996; 707845; 2 Folders (Box 453)
          1996-13
        - California, 1959, undated; 707844 (Box 453)
        - Connecticut, 1962-1964; 707843; 4 Folders (Box 453)
          1964-06, 1964-09
        - Connecticut, 1965-1973; 707842; 3 Folders (Box 454)
          1965-09, 1973-02
        - New York City, 1950-1958; 707841; 2 Folders (Box 454)
        - New York City, 1962-1970; 707840; 4 Folders (Box 455)
          1962-31, 1963-23, 1965-16, 1965-19, 1968-07
        - New York City, 1986-1998; 707839; 10 Folders (Box 456)
          1986-03, 1991-06, 1997-04
        - New York City, 1997; 707838; 4 Folders (Box 457)
          1997-04
        - New York City, 1998-2000; 707837; 2 Folders (Box 457)
          1998-03
        - Road trip to Reno, 1960; 707836; 4 Folders (Box 458)
        - General, 707818
          - Miscellaneous, 1960-1995; 707835 (Box 459)
            1960-15, 1965-08, 1975-11
          - Tucson, Arizona, 1997; 707834 (Box 459)
            1997-15
          - Florida, 1957; 707833 (Box 459)
            1957-02
          - Kansas, 1995; 707832 (Box 459)
            1995-01
          - Maine, 1974; 707831 (Box 459)
            1974-13
          - Boston, Cambridge, 1956; 707830 (Box 459)
            1956-07
          - Nantucket, 1978-1983; 707829; 2 Folders (Box 459)
            1978-10, 1979-03, 1983-05, 1983-06
          - Minnesota, 1990; 707828 (Box 460)
          - Saint Louis, 1986; 707827 (Box 460)
            1986-15
          - Jersey City, New Jersey, 1990; 1994; 707826 (Box 460)
          - Montauk, New York, 1963; 707825 (Box 460)
            1963-28
          - New York state, 1964-1965; 707824 (Box 460)
            1964-25, 1965-17
          - Oregon, 1973; 707823 (Box 460)
            1973-05
          - South Carolina, 1980; 707822 (Box 460)
            1980-07
          - Texas, 1961; 707821 (Box 460)
            1961-06
          - Utah, 1991; 707820 (Box 460)
            1991-01
          - Vermont, Massachusetts, New England, 1970-1984; 707819 (Box 460)
            1970-06
      - Latin America, 707806
        - Mexico, 707813
          - Guadalupe Cathedral, Mexico City, Janitzio, Diego Rivera fresco at Palacio Nacional, Frida Kahlo museum, Monte Alban, Uxmal, 1959-1968; 707816; 5 Folders (Box 461)
            1959-03, 1959-04, 1968-04
          - Chichén Itzá, Villa Hermosa, Lake Pátzcuaro, Mitla, Monte Alban, Oaxaca, Uxmal, Vera Cruz, 1959; 707815; 4 Folders (Box 462)
            1959-05, 1959-06
          - Mexican Artists: Pedro Coronel, Maka, Jimenez, Frida Kahlo, Lola Olmedo, Leonora Carrington, Rosa Covarrubias, Carlos Pellicer, Carlos Chavez, Carlos Fuentes, Senora Maria Josefina Montes de Oca Quijada, Salvador Novo, Evgeny Yevtushenko, Alvaro Siqueiros, Jose Revueltos, Marco Antonio Montes de Oca, 1960-1968; 707814; 3 Folders (Box 463)
            1960-04, 1968-04
        - South America, 707811
          - Santiago, Buenos Aries, Caracas, Colombia, Bogota, 1981-1982; 707812; 3 Folders (Box 463)
            1982-02, 1982-04
        - Caribbean, 707807
          - Antigua, Barbados, Haiti, St. Lucia, 1979-1997; 707810; 5 Folders (Box 464)
            1994-02, 1995-02
          - Cuba, 2000; 707809 (Box 464)
          - "Santo Domingo," Dominican Republic, undated; 707808 (Box 464)
      - Middle East, 707779
        - "Refugee Story," Israel, 1960; 707805; 3 Folders (Box 465)
        - Iran, 707800
          - Tehran, 1956; 707804; 2 Folders (Box 465)
            1956-09, includes 4 by 5 inches transparencies
          - Palace, refineries, carpets, outskirts of Isfahan, 1956; 707803; 4 Folders (Box 466)
          - Nomads and villages near Shiraz; Qazvin, Pasargadae, Yazd, Cham, Qom, Tabriz, Varamin, Alborz mountains, 1956; 707802; 3 Folders (Box 467)
          - Alborz mountains, 1956; 707801; 2 Folders (Box 467)
        - Lebanon, 707798
          - Beirut, Kadisha valley, cedars, Baalbek, Byblos, Beit ed-Dine, 1956; 707799; 4 Folders (Box 468)
            1956-10A
        - Jordan, 707796
          - Jerusalem, Petra, Wadi Araba, Jerash, 1956; 707797; 2 Folders (Box 469)
            1956-10B
        - Iraq, 707794
          - Baghdad, Tigris and Euphrates, 1956; 707795 (Box 469)
            1956-10C
        - Syria, 707792
          - Damascus, Palmyra, Krak des Chevaliers, 1956; 707793 (Box 469)
            1956-10D
        - Israel, 707790
          - Jaffa, Sea of Galilee, Jerusalem from citadel, artists, 1972; 707791; 2 Folders (Box 470)
        - Tunisia, 707785
          - Tunisia story list, handwritten, 1957; 1960; 707789 (Box 470)
          - Ruins, Jaune Tunisie, 1959; 707788; 2 Folders (Box 470)
            1959-31
          - Landscapes, political meeting, date palms, Ghar El Melh - Porto Farina, nomads, Matmata, Carthage Punic port, 1959-1960; 707787; 4 Folders (Box 471)
            1959-31, 1960-25
          - Mahdia, Hammamet, El Duem, Carthage, Roman ruins, mosaics and art, 1960; 707786; 4 Folders (Box 472)
            1960-25
        - Egypt, 707780
          - Egypt, Cairo-Nile, 1981; 707784; 2 Folders (Box 473)
            1981-02, 8 by 10 inches transparencies
          - Egypt, Cairo-Nile, 1981; 707783; 2 Folders (Box 473)
          - Egypt, Cairo-Nile, 1981; 707782; 4 Folders (Box 474)
          - Egypt, Cairo-Nile, 1981; 707781; 4 Folders (Box 475)
      - Africa general, South Africa, 707773
        - South Africa 4 by 5 inches transparencies, undated; 707778 (Box 475)
        - South Africa, 1955; 707777; 2 Folders (Box 475)
        - Capetown, Johannesburg, Nelson Mandela, 1990; 707776; 3 Folders (Box 476)
          1990-14
        - "Sabi-Sabi", undated; 707775 (Box 476)
        - Wildlife, undated; 707774 (Box 476)
      - Asia, 707752
        - China, 707767
          - China, 1978-1979; 707772; 2 Folders (Box 477)
            1978-12, 1978-98, 1979-137
          - China, 1979; 707771; 2 Folders (Box 477)
            1979-05
          - Tai Shan, Qufu, Beijing and some Salesman in Beijing, 1983; 707770; 4 Folders (Box 478)
            1983-08
          - Beijing, 1987; 707769 (Box 479)
          - Duplicates, 1978-1983; 707768 (Box 479)
        - Japan, 707757
          - Kyoto, 1970; 707766 (Box 479)
          - Hiroshima, Miyajima (also known as Itsukushima), Inland Sea, Beppu, Usuki, Mt. Aso, 1977; 707765 (Box 479)
            1977-12
          - Kyoto, Tokyo; shrines, tea ceremony, 1996; 707764 (Box 479)
            1996-05, 1996-06
          - Takarazuka Theater and school, 1977; 707763; 4 Folders (Box 480)
          - Takarazuka Theater and school, 1977; 707762; 2 Folders (Box 481)
          - Takarazuka Theater, 1977; 707761 (Box 481)
          - Takarazuka Theater and school, 1977; 707760; 2 Folders (Box 482)
            1977-11
          - Takarazuka Theatre, 1984; 707759 (Box 482)
            1984-07
          - Takarazuka Theatre, Gone with the wind, 1977-1984; 707758 (Box 483)
            1977-11, 1984-07
        - India, 707753
          - India, 1993; 707756; 2 Folders (Box 483)
          - Paro, Taj Mahal, circa 1993; 707755 (Box 484)
          - India/Bhutan, 1993; 707754; 5 Folders (Box 484)
      - Films, Plays, and Projects, 707713
        - Arthur Miller Plays, 707729
          - Lincoln Center, After the Fall, 1963; 707751 (Box 485)
          - The American Clock, 1963; 707750 (Box 485)
          - Broken Glass, 1994; 707749 (Box 485)
          - The Creation of the World, 1972; 707748; 2 Folders (Box 485)
            1972-06
          - The Crucible, film version, 1995; 707747 (Box 485)
          - Death of a Salesman, 707741 (Box 485)
            - Beijing, 1983; 707746; 3 Folders (Box 486)
            - "Dustin Hoffman becomes Willy Loman, Broadway Production", 1983; 707745 (Box 487)
              1983-13
            - Chicago, 1984; 707744; 2 Folders (Box 487)
              1984-02, [1984-52]
            - Shooting of Death of a Salesman movie with Dustin Hoffman, directed by Volker Schlondorf, 1985; 707743; 3 Folders (Box 488)
              1985-02
            - Shooting of Death of a Salesman movie with Dustin Hoffman, directed by Volker Schlondorf, 1985; 707742 (Box 489)
          - Elegy for a Lady, staged at Long Wharf Theater, New Haven with Christine Lahti and Charles Cioffi, Arthur Miller directing, 1982; 707740 (Box 490)
            1982-13
          - A Memory of Two Mondays, 1970; 707739 (Box 490)
            1970-13
          - The Misfits, 1960; 707738 (Box 490)
          - The Price, 1967; 707737 (Box 490)
            1967-12
          - Playing for Time, television production, 1979; 707736 (Box 490)
            1979-16
          - The Reason Why, 1967-1969; 707735 (Box 491)
            1967-07
          - The Ride Down Mount Morgan, London, 1991; 707734 (Box 491)
            1991-10
          - The Ride Down Mount Morgan, set, 1996; 707733 (Box 491)
            1996-12
          - Some Kind of Love Story, 1982; 707732 (Box 491)
            1982-13, Staged at Long Wharf Theater, New Haven with Christine Lahti and Charles Cioffi, and Arthur Miller directing
          - Up from Paradise, musical production, Jewish Repertory Theatre, New York City, 1983; 707731 (Box 491)
            1983-18
          - The View from the Bridge, film, 1961; 707730 (Box 491)
            1961-11
        - Books, 707724
          - Donau and a sheet of duplicates, circa 1995; 707728; 3 Folders (Box 492)
          - Pamplona, 1954; 707727 (Box 493)
          - Portraits, circa 1977; 707726 (Box 493)
          - Russia, 1967-1989; 707725; 2 Folders (Box 493)
        - Films and Television Productions, 707714
          - Aimez-Vous Brahms?, 1960; 707723 (Box 494)
          - Chantilly Lace, 1992; 707722 (Box 494)
          - The Journey, starring Yul Brynner and directed by Anatole Litvak, 1958; 707721 (Box 494)
            1958-10
          - Moulin Rouge, starring José Ferrer and directed by John Huston, 1953; 707720 (Box 494)
            1953-10
          - Prisoner without a Name, Cell without a Number, 1983; 707719 (Box 494)
            1983-02
          - The Royal Romance of Charles and Diana, 1982; 707718 (Box 494)
            1982-06
          - Solomon and Sheba, starring Yul Brynner and directed by King Vidor, 1958; 707717 (Box 494)
          - Taras Bulba, starring Yul Brynner, 1961; 707716; 2 Folders (Box 495)
            1961-52
          - The Unforgiven, 1959; 707715 (Box 495)
            1959-06
      - Portraits, 707650
        - Portraits, Magnum 500 scans, 1954-1990; 707712; 2 Folders (Box 496)
        - Artists/Writers, 1969-1987; 707711 (Box 496)
        - "American Women", 1955; 707710 (Box 496)
          1955-16
        - Arp, Jean, 1956; 707709 (Box 496)
        - Berg, Nancy, 1956; 707708 (Box 496)
        - Bourgeois, Louise, 1970-1998; 707707 (Box 496)
        - Brynner, Yul, circa 1960; 707706; 4 by 5 inches transparency (Box 497)
        - Brynner, Yul, 1958-1985; 707705 (Box 497)
          1958-10, 1959-09, 1959-19, 1960-05, 1960-26
        - "B" General, 1959-1995; 707704 (Box 497)
        - "C" General, 1956-1975; 707703 (Box 497)
          Includes: Doris Caesar, Martha Clarke, Joan Copeland, Frederick Cripps
        - Calder, Alexander, 1964-1979; 707702 (Box 497)
        - Calder, Alexander, 1967-1994; 707701 (Box 498)
        - Caldwell, Zoe: Stratford Shakespeare Festival, 1967; 707700 (Box 498)
        - Douglas, Kirk, 1959; 707699 (Box 498)
        - Doyle, Tom, 1995; 707698 (Box 498)
          1995-05
        - Duchess of Kent in Mexico, 1959; 707697 (Box 498)
          1959-03
        - Dunaway, Faye, 1963; 707696 (Box 498)
          1963-36
        - "G" General, 1967; 1995; 707695 (Box 499)
          1967-07, 1995-08, 1995-09
        - "H" General, 1958-1961; 707694 (Box 499)
          Hartung, Hans: 1958-05; Hammerskjold, Dag: 1961-10
        - Hepburn, Audrey, 1959; 707693 (Box 499)
        - Hoffman, Dustin, 1983; 707692 (Box 499)
        - Jeanmarie, Zizi, 1957; 707691; 2 Folders (Box 499)
          Also includes 4 by 5 inches transparencies
        - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1964; 707690 (Box 499)
          1964-13
        - Jong, Erica, 1983; 707689 (Box 499)
        - "K" General, 1959-1967; 707688 (Box 500)
          Kaufman, Christine: 1961-52; Kleiner, Doris: 1959-28; Kosygin, Alexei: 1967-07
        - Liberman, [1974-1985]; 707687 (Box 500)
        - Lichtenstein, Roy, 1997; 707686 (Box 500)
          1997-07
        - Lurcat, Jean (in St. Cere), 1957; 707685 (Box 500)
          1957-08
        - MacIver, Loren (studio), 1956; 707684 (Box 500)
          1956-04
        - Mansfield, Jane, 1956-1959; 707683 (Box 500)
          1956-07, 1959-07
        - Marisol, 1995; 707682 (Box 500)
          1995-10
        - Miller, Jean, 1963; 707681 (Box 500)
          1963-30
        - Moore, Henry, 1954; 707680 (Box 501)
          1954-08
        - Moore, Honor, 1995; 707679 (Box 501)
          1995-15
        - Nesterova, Natalia, 1989; 707678 (Box 501)
          1989-10
        - Newmar, Julie, 1961; 707677 (Box 501)
          1961-30
        - Onassis, Tina, 1956; 707676 (Box 501)
          1956-11
        - Osborne, Robert, Iberian Bronzes, 1974; 707675 (Box 501)
        - Ox, Jack, 1995; 707674 (Box 501)
        - Pleasant, Corby, 1965; 707673 (Box 501)
          1965-15
        - Picasso, 1954; 707672 (Box 501)
        - Plummer, Christopher: Stratford Shakespeare Festival, 1967; 707671 (Box 501)
        - Prachensky, Markus, 1975; 707670 (Box 501)
          1975-09
        - Price, Vincent, 1959; 707669 (Box 502)
        - Quinn, Anthony, 1959; 707668 (Box 502)
        - Reissman, Michael, 1990; 707667 (Box 502)
          1990-07
        - Robards, Jason, 1963; 707666 (Box 502)
          4 by 4 inches transparencies: 1963-26
        - Roth, Phillip, 1983; 707665 (Box 502)
          1983-15, [1983-254]
        - Rubenstein, Helena, 1957; 707664 (Box 502)
          1957-09
        - Selassie, Haile, 1967; 1989; 707663 (Box 502)
          1967-04, 1989-75
        - Schiaffino, Rosanna, 1960-1967; 707662 (Box 502)
          1960-07
        - Schnabel, Julian, 1985; 707661 (Box 502)
        - Serling, Rod, 1959; 707660 (Box 502)
        - Steinberg, Saul: Masks, 1961-1966; 707659 (Box 503)
          1961-04, 1962-32, 1966-14
        - Styron, William, 1967; 1981; 707658 (Box 503)
          1967-02, 1981-60
        - Tekle, Afewerk, 1987; 707657 (Box 503)
        - Vanderbilt, Gloria, 1967; 707656 (Box 503)
          1967-04
        - Vassar, Angela, undated; 707655 (Box 503)
        - Voznesensky, Andrei, 1966-1985; 707654 (Box 503)
          1966-05, 1971-01, 1975-16, 1977-18, 1985-01
        - Walcott, Derek, 1994; 707653 (Box 503)
          1994-02
        - Wesselman, Tom, 1995; 707652 (Box 503)
          1995-08
        - Woytuk, Peter, 1995-08; 707651 (Box 503)
      - Personal, 707555
        - Houses, 707643
          - La Reinere Balenciaga country house, 1959; 707649 (Box 504)
            1959-15
          - Bernard Buffet house, 1957; 707648 (Box 504)
          - Shu's guest house, barn and study, undated; 707647; 3 Folders (Box 504)
          - Knoll house, undated; 707646; 2 Folders (Box 504)
          - Knoll house tennis barn, undated; 707645 (Box 504)
          - Stillman house, 1973; 707644 (Box 504)
        - Nature, 707635
          - Wild vines, 1974 July; 707642 (Box 505)
          - Roses of Sackville West; blueberries, flowers, 1961-1990; 707641 (Box 505)
            1961-16, 1973-02
          - Birds, 1987 July; 707640 (Box 505)
          - Animals: springer spaniels, peacocks, horses, squirrels, and a frog, 1978; 707639 (Box 505)
          - Bees and butterflies from Connecticut, 1973; 707638 (Box 505)
            1973-02
          - Florida animals, 1970; 707637 (Box 505)
          - Elephant "tea party", 1989; 707636 (Box 505)
            1989-14: Creation of Martha Clarke's Ballet with animals, "Endangered Species" in South Carolina and Connecticut.
        - Arts, 707628
          - Atalbot, sculptures, 1975; 707634 (Box 506)
          - Mixed artwork, 1957, undated; 707633 (Box 506)
          - Vionnet, Madeleine: Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1974; 707632 (Box 506)
          - Xhosa jewelry, undated; 707631 (Box 506)
          - Rehearsal shots of Ballet "Vienna Lusthaus" conceived and directed by Martha Clarke, 1986; 707630 (Box 506)
            1986-04
          - Studies of Nudes, 1973; 707629; 2 Folders (Box 506)
        - General, 707617
          - Portraits, 1982, undated; 707627 (Box 507)
          - People, 1965; 1995; 707626 (Box 507)
            1965-14
          - Miscellaneous, 1972-1981; 707625 (Box 507)
          - Wien-Sculptor-Lobau/Donau, Linz, Wachau, undated; 707624 (Box 507)
          - Bellevue, 1981; 707623 (Box 507)
          - Special locations, 1996-1997; 707622 (Box 507)
          - Haidplatz (Tere): Car show, church, carnival fireworks, undated; 707621 (Box 507)
          - Mixed images, 1974-1982, undated; 707620; 7 Folders (Box 508)
          - 4 by 5 inches color negatives, sixteen negatives, [1998]; 707619 (Box 508)
            Includes 2 prints
          - Black-and-white portfolio, 1954-1987; 707618; 5 Folders (Box 509)
        - Family and Friends, 707596
          - Arthur Miller: Portraits, 707613 (Box 509)
            Arthur Miller in Roxbury, Connecticut, and during travels, as well as with family, friends, and associates.
            - Color and black-and-white contact sheets, 1985-1986; 707616 (Box 510)
            - Roxbury, Columbia, Hout Bay, South Africa, 1965-1999; 707615; 4 Folders (Box 510)
              1971-01, 1977-01, 1980-12, 1987-253
            - At home in Roxbury, Manhattan, Urbino, 1983-1992; 707614; 5 Folders (Box 511)
              1983-34, 1988-07, 1987-253, 1988-073
          - Inge Morath: Portraits, 1957-1983; 707612 (Box 512)
            Images of clippings by or about Morath; and photographs of Morath taken by Arthur Miller. Includes Paris, 1957-15
          - "Great Austrian State Prize for photography," dupes, 1992; 707611 (Box 512)
          - Rebecca Miller, 707606 (Box 512)
            - Rebecca Miller, 1962-1965; 707610; 4 Folders (Box 512)
              1962-43, 1963-04, 1964-06, 1965-01, 1965-09
            - "Rebecca with Arthur", 1965; 707609 (Box 513)
            - "Young Rebecca", 1965-1972; 707608; 2 Folders (Box 513)
              1965-08, 1966-07, 1967-01, 1971-01
            - "Personal: Rebecca", 1972-1974; 707607; 3 Folders (Box 513)
              1988-323
          - Miller family, 1974-1989; 707605; 3 Folders (Box 514)
          - "Arthur and Inge", circa 1980-1990; 707604 (Box 514)
          - "Fishers Island", 1970; 707603 (Box 514)
          - "Gone Fishing", 707602 (Box 514)
          - "A wedding, a graduation", 1974 June; 707601 (Box 514)
          - "Wedding", 1981; 707600 (Box 514)
          - "The Pascal family", 1988; 707599 (Box 514)
            1988-01
          - "Miller Snapshots: Debra Winger, Ezra Swerslow, Jeremy Thomas", [1988]; 707598 (Box 514)
          - Martha's Vineyard, 1984 August; 707597 (Box 514)
        - Connecticut, 1960-1967; 707579; 2 Folders
          1967-01
          - Nature, woods, 1967; 707595 (Box 515)
          - Plants, flowers, 1967; 707594 (Box 515)
          - Winter, 1967; 707593; 2 Folders (Box 515)
          - Washington, Roxbury, 1969-1970; 707592 (Box 515)
            1969-01, 1970-01
          - Houses, Mystic, Roxbury, 1970; 707591 (Box 516)
          - Avon, Washington, Salisbury, 1971; 707590 (Box 516)
            1971-01
          - Roxbury, Aerial views of estate, 1972; 707589 (Box 516)
          - Fall, Brooklyn, 1973; 707588 (Box 516)
          - Autumn, Shephaug River, Stonington, 1974; 707587 (Box 516)
            1974-01
          - Animals, ducks, horses, grocery store, Connecticut River, Apple Blossom Fair, 1974; 707586 (Box 516)
          - Essex, Clapp wedding, Rumsey Hall School, 1975; 707585 (Box 517)
            1975-01
          - Roxbury: winter, morels, gardens, 1977-1978; 707584 (Box 517)
            1977-01, 1978-01
          - Roxbury, 1985-1989; 707583 (Box 517)
            1989-01
          - Roxbury: winter/spring, 1990-1991; 707582 (Box 517)
            1990-01, 1991-01